I'd like to thank you for this day and I'd like to thank you for each person here.
I ask God that you be with this community and bless it.
I pray God that you will be with our country and bless it.
I thank you for the Council members and I pray God that the decision may not be pleased with you.
I ask that you bless God with His family.
I pray for the people that have been affected by COVID.
I ask that you give them strength and peace and comfort.
God I thank you for your sentient Jesus Christ.
It's in His name, I pray.
Amen.
Thank you.
Now, there's a CC-2011 back there, a group in the United
Financial Support, and a B-way for the peace of dear
President, Chris B. and Ben, and Chris B. and Ben here.
But this track, she is not here.
This is giving the same incentives that we did for
fresh energy.
We'd like to build and sustain the energy
see if requires a bit of them that they need certain payroll guidelines to keep your period.
You just want to be conversely.
And if they don't do that, then they have to try to make it go ahead and pay various fees
that you're waiting with this resolution.
It's an incentive for somebody who's wanting to pay in business.
They're not going to be going to employ 14 and a half or 15 people.
They're committing to at least that.
They do the question well.
They do it for you.
I want to give time.
Thank you.
All those things.
Just fine.
I just...
three weeks ago, the last walk in Main Street. We got black face put them, which is basically
the coarse aggregate layer that goes on top of your base, and had a bunch of trapped groundwater
in there that was causing our base to pump underneath the favors. So, Olson and Anderson both
kind of got together. Look at this and we're recommending that it's all in a French frame.
It will basically run just in front of the curved bedding line from the south side of the
third up to the influence of the front camper. So, we're going to put in two four inch
perperated lines. And that whole trench wrapped in a filter fabric, and then they put a clean
rock inside of there. So, it wants to suck water out of the base and into a low point.
And we're hoping that it doesn't let us stabilize. So, Franco gave us a cost at four bucks of
foot, or 500 feet of it. And then there's another ultimate in there for 30, 100 in facing
back in the place, the old brick and wood. And if they can get tied into it, everything's fine. We even,
but we're putting that in in the C-dition case, we'll be with a place that I'm going to give you. Any questions?
So, is this scenario that's already been at a overlay on it that you're going to take back
up? We didn't even get paid even on it. We stopped before they ever got. You couldn't even get
a truck back down it to get that spot later. It kept pumping so bad. But the area right next to it
that ass bump on it. So, they're salt cutting a little bit of that direction after that. They
didn't get it. I started at any time. They had a crew of people trying to get it through
breaks in the weather as much as possible. So, I think Kevin said they had a couple hundred people
late all day at that. So, they're trucking around home with it.
I don't know if I saw it. I didn't like the fact that we back in the 20,000, but I do appreciate
the fact that you guys noticed a problem. So, a cost of selection of picks up now to give them
a better problem with the future. So, I appreciate you guys to bring that to our tips.
given the amount, given the number of items.
Yeah, we honestly have no idea where this water is coming from.
When we was in there a couple of years ago putting in water
on it, never seeing anything, everything to dry.
And then as soon as I'm going to three days
having a phase drop, I'm going to start
with some Instagram water issue.
And it's just going to lay track in there.
So this will at least give a way to get out.
Much of the debris.
Second.
Part of it?
Thanks.
Thank you.
We're glad that the debris business is ending.
This is really good.
13, trustee in the announcement.
14, and turn it.
Second.
Part of it?